gdiapers.com 2009-11-30

# gDiapers - privacy policy

## Privacy Policy

gDiapers and its subsidiaries (collectively, "Company") recognize privacy as an important issue and have prepared this Privacy Policy to inform you of our data collection and use practices and confirm our commitment to keep your personal information secure. 

As Company services evolve, we may revise this policy, so please check back frequently. If you have questions about Company privacy practices please contact us at [info@gdiapers.com](mailto:info@gdiapers.com). 

Please note that this policy only applies to our data collection and use practices for the Company websites and our other products and services and does not apply to the data collection and use practices of other companies or organizations whose products, services or websites you may use or gain access through the Company websites. For information on the data collection and use practices of those third parties, please refer to their respective policies and procedures. 

**Information Collection and Use  
**Company collects personally identifiable information when you register for a Company account, and when you use certain Company products and services. Company may also receive personally identifiable information from its resellers and other business partners. 

When you register with Company, we ask for your contact information (such as your name, street address and email address), as well as certain information pertaining to your business, along with billing information such as a bank account and/or credit card number. 

Company uses the information collected to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to process payment transactions, to facilitate billing, and otherwise deliver the payment gateway services. We may also send merchants service announcements, newsletters, and periodic notices about specials and new products. 

Personally identifiable consumer information is used to process payment transactions and for no other purpose. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
In general, we do not sell, rent or otherwise trade your personal information with third parties for compensation. However, we may disclose and share your personal information with third parties under the following limited circumstances. 

Company will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 1) we have your consent to share the information; 2) we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; 3) we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Company to provide a product or service to you (unless we tell you differently these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide them beyond what is necessary to assist us). 

Personally identifiable consumer information is shared with third parties (such as banks and credit card processors) to the extent necessary for Company to deliver payment processing services. 

We also may release personally identifiable information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Merchant Agreement and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and risk reduction. 

In the event that Company is acquired, merchant account information may be one of the transferred assets. 

**Cookies**  
When you visit a Company website, one or more cookies, web beacons or action tags may be sent to your computer or otherwise used in connection with your visit or use. A cookie is a small data file that is sent to your computer by a website when you visit. When stored on your computer, a cookie uniquely identifies your browser and records your preferences and other data about your visit. Cookies are also sometimes used to complete transactions requested by users. Web beacons, also known as web bugs, are small, graphic images that transparently reside on a website or other web-based service and are designed to allow the website or service owner to monitor who is visiting the website or using the service. Action tags assist in delivering cookies and embed a random identifying number on a user's browser. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. For a session cookie, once you close your browser the cookie simply terminates. 

A persistent cookie stays stored on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can change the settings on your browser to refuse or notify you prior to accepting cookies and to remove them from your computer. However, some features, products and services may not function properly without cookies. 

**Information Storage and Security**  
We have implemented and use a variety of industry accepted physical, electronic and managerial policies and procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect to help prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction and to maintain its accuracy and correct use. We generally store the information and data we collect on our own servers in a secure environment and restrict access to your personal information to employees and agents who need to know that information in order to provide you with access and use of the Company websites, operate and maintain the Company websites and as otherwise set forth and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. While we have taken efforts to safeguard and secure your personal information, we cannot guarantee that your information may not be disclosed, altered or destroyed by accidental circumstances or by the unauthorized acts of others. 

**Special Notification with respect to Children's Privacy (Users under the Age of 13)**  
In response to concerns about protecting children's privacy online, Congress enacted the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), which sets forth rules and procedures governing the ways in which websites may collect, use and disclose any personal information for children under the age of 13. In accordance with Company policy and COPPA regulations, we DO NOT: 

  * Request or knowingly collect personally identifiable information online or offline contact information from users under 13 years of age; or 
  * Knowingly use or share personal information from users under 13 years of age with third parties; It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately delete the information from our servers.

Questions regarding children's privacy should be directed to us at the contact information provided at the end of this privacy policy. 

**Enforcement**  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please direct them to us at the contact information provided below. We have instituted internal policies and procedures for handling such submissions and will respond to you in a timely manner. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry, or if it is not satisfactorily addressed, you may contact the Federal Trade Commission for further action on your complaint at <http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/>. 

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**  
We will change, amend and update this Privacy Policy and the privacy policies of the various Company websites from time to time to reflect changes in our privacy practices, technology, products and services, general business operations and industry. In the event of any such change, we will post a revised policy on this website or the website of the respective product or service and revise the "Last Updated" date of such policy. We reserve the right to change, amend and update this Privacy Policy, including all of our associated privacy policies, at any time in our sole and absolute discretion, and such changes will be effective upon posting of the revised policy. In the event of a material change in our information collection and use practices, we will provide more prominent notice of such change along with the revision to the effective date of the policy. You should check this Privacy Policy and the policies of the Company Sites and other Company Properties you may access or use on a regular basis to ensure you have reviewed and are familiar with the most current policy. 

**Contacting Us**  
For any questions or concerns you may have regarding this Privacy Policy and our information and data collection and use practices, please contact us at: 

**Via Mail**  
gDiapers  
PO Box 10106  
Portland, Oregon   
97296  
USA 

**Via Email:** [info@gdiapers.com](mailto:info@gdiapers.com)  

Last revised: 29th June, 2005
